const ModuleThreeQuestions = () => {
    return [
        {
            questionText: "Cryptocurrency is:",
            correctAnswer: "a fully digital currency",
            answers: [
                'a fully digital currency',
                'a currency of coins located in Silicon Valley',
                'physical money backerd up in the cloud',
                'all owned by the company that founded it'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "Just like all currencies, cryptocurrency is affected by inflation",
            correctAnswer: "False",
            answers: [
                'True',
                'False'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "How do you create Bitcoin?",
            correctAnswer: "You mine it",
            answers: [
                'You ask for it',
                'You mine it',
                'You find it on the web',
                'You dig it up'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "Is Bitcoin an anonymous way to pay for things?",
            correctAnswer: "semi - if people know your address they can see what you\'ve spent",
            answers: [
                'Yes - completely anonymous',
                'No - completely non-anonymous',
                'semi - if people know your address they can see what you\'ve spent',
                'semi - if people know your address they can see where you live'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "What is cryptography?",
            correctAnswer: "A method of using encryption and decryption to secure data",
            answers: [
                'The study of ancient maps',
                'A method of using encryption and decryption to secure data',
                'A digital map to where you can find cryptocurrencies',
                'The structure of the network that maintains a cryptocurrency'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "Who can create a new cryptocurrency?",
            correctAnswer: "Anyone with the technology",
            answers: [
                'Anyone with the technology',
                'A person or persons who stakes the overall value of the created currency with another form of currency',
                'A person or persons with explicit permission',
                'A technology company of LLC'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "What can you purchase with cryptocurrency?",
            correctAnswer: "Anything and everything",
            answers: [
                'Only drugs on the black market',
                'Only digital items like songs, movies and games',
                'Any purchases made online',
                'Anything and everything'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "Which of the following is not a benefit of cryptocurrencies over traditional currencies we/'ve been using for centuries?",
            correctAnswer: "You cannot lose your currency because it\'s stored on a server",
            answers: [
                'There is a limit to how many units of the currency can exist',
                'There is no central operating facility holding power over users',
                'Transfer of funds are easilty verified and hard to forge',
                'You cannot lose your currency because it\'s stored on a server'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "Which cryptocurrency is used to create decentralized applications?",
            correctAnswer: "Ethereum",
            answers: [
                'Bitcoin',
                'Ethereum',
                'Litecoin',
                'Dogecoin'
            ],
        },
        {
            questionText: "Cryptocurrency can be used to hide criminal activity",
            correctAnswer: "True",
            answers: [
                'True',
                'False'
            ],
        },
    ]
}

module.exports = ModuleThreeQuestions;